The city's humming, the lights are low. I'm
waiting for you, I'm ready to go. The rain is
tapping on the glass. I knew this feeling would
fail to last. I hear your footsteps in the hall.
I'm not afraid to fall. This is the only thing I
know is true. You've got my neon heart shining
for you in the dark. A love so bright, it's all the
choice. You've got my neon heart. It's an
electric color feeling, and it all starts with
you.
We're walking fast on the wet concrete The
rhythm matches with our eyes meet Don't need a
promise, don't need a vow My only moment is right
here, right now I hear your footsteps in the hall
I'm not afraid to fall This is the only thing I
know is true You've got my neon heart Shining for
you in the dark A love so bright it's off the
charts You've got my neon heart It's an electric
color feeling And it all starts with you
City sleep, we're wide awake A chance that we're
both gonna take
You've got my neon heart shining, shining for
you. In the dark, a love so bright, it's off the
charts. You've got my neon heart. It's an
electric color feeling, and it all starts with
you. You. My neon heart. Heart, heart, heart,
heart.
My neon heart.